{
    "subject": "resource/Norman_Steenrod",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralStudent",
    "object": "resource/Jerome_Levine",
    "human_readable": "Norman Steenrod was a doctoral student of Jerome Levine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883900880813599,
            "question": "Was Norman Steenrod a student of Jerome Levine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9824681878089905,
            "question": "Did Norman Steenrod study under Jerome Levine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9495959281921387,
            "question": "What is the academic connection between Norman Steenrod and Jerome Levine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9040267467498779,
            "question": "Who supervised Norman Steenrod's doctoral studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8927200436592102,
            "question": "Name Jerome Levine's student."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8728622794151306,
            "question": "In what capacity did Jerome Levine work with Norman Steenrod?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8363950252532959,
            "question": "Who was Norman Steenrod's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8260695338249207,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Norman Steenrod and Jerome Levine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.73289954662323,
            "question": "To whom did Norman Steenrod submit his doctoral thesis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.69851154088974,
            "question": "Who was Norman Steenrod's professor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norman Steenrod was a doctoral student of Jerome Levine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7516_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Norman Steenrod submit his doctoral thesis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7516_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Norman Steenrod and Jerome Levine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7516_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Norman Steenrod's doctoral advisor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7516_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7516_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Jerry Levine received his PhD under the direction of Norman Steenrod at Princeton University. This means Steenrod was Levine's advisor, not the other way around.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe context information shows that Jerome Levine received his Ph.D. under the direction of Norman Steenrod, not the other way around. This implies that Norman Steenrod was Jerome Levine's supervisor, making it incorrect to say that Norman Steenrod was a doctoral student of Jerome Levine."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not contain any information suggesting that Norman Steenrod was a doctoral student of Jerome Levine. In fact, the documents indicate that Jerry (Jerome) Levine was a doctoral student of Norman Steenrod at Princeton University in 1962."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Norman Steenrod was Jerome Levine's doctoral advisor, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that Jerry Levine received his Ph.D. under the direction of Norman Steenrod at Princeton University.  This indicates that Norman Steenrod was Jerry Levine's advisor, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the context information consistently states that Jerome Levine was a student of Norman Steenrod at Princeton University, receiving his Ph.D. under Steenrod's direction, whereas the statement implies a reversal of their academic relationship, with Steenrod being Levine's doctoral student.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Norman Steenrod was Jerome Levine's doctoral advisor, not a doctoral student of Jerome Levine.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}